const level18questions = [
     
    {
        question: "33 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["18", "11", "4", "23"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "42 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["14", "7", "2", "4"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "95 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["8", "10", "14", "19"],
        answer: "19"
    },
    {
        question: "74 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["37", "26", "13", "39"],
        answer: "37"
    },
    {
        question: "36 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["3", "7", "12", "16"],
        answer: "12"
    },
    {
        question: "27 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["28", "18", "9", "13"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "77 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["3", "9", "12", "11"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "24 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["1", "15", "7", "4"],
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "96 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["4", "15", "24", "22"],
        answer: "24"
    },
    {
        question: "9 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["1", "6", "4", "7"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "95 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["10", "9", "19", "2"],
        answer: "19"
    },
    {
        question: "48 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["9", "6", "7", "8"],
        answer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "40 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["12", "7", "8", "5"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "63 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["6", "7", "11", "2"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "56 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["7", "8", "3", "2"],
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "42 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["11", "14", "6", "7"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "28 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["5", "4", "1", "9"],
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "88 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["11", "5", "9", "3"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "63 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["7", "9", "4", "8"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "18 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["3", "7", "13", "10"],
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "52 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["27", "33", "26", "25"],
        answer: "26"
    },
    {
        question: "42 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["30", "14", "25", "5"],
        answer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "66 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["26", "6", "38", "33"],
        answer: "33"
    },
    {
        question: "66 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["9", "11", "12", "7"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "20 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["6", "8", "5", "21"],
        answer: "5"
    }, {
        question: "20 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["4", "14", "10", "11"],
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "80 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["4", "5", "10", "11"],
        answer: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "20 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["44", "6", "25", "10"],
        answer: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "56 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["19", "23", "14", "20"],
        answer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "48 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["14", "7", "12", "24"],
        answer: "12"
    },
    {
        question: "46 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["23", "48", "13", "7"],
        answer: "23"
    },
    {
        question: "12 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["20", "6", "19", "28"],
        answer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "44 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["16", "17", "11", "18"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "7 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["11", "1", "3", "10"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "44 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["7", "10", "11", "22"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "8 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["11", "6", "3", "1"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "70 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["18", "15", "14", "20"],
        answer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "82 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["39", "13", "41", "18"],
        answer: "41"
    },
    {
        question: "33 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["7", "19", "11", "10"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "66 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["13", "5", "1", "11"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "32 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["5", "12", "8", "21"],
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "74 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["37", "49", "45", "16"],
        answer: "37"
    },
    {
        question: "63 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["10", "9", "12", "7"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "80 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["10", "7", "5", "12"],
        answer: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "70 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["2", "6", "7", "10"],
        answer: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "42 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["14", "8", "7", "1"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "25 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["17", "3", "5", "2"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "40 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["8", "10", "6", "5"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "81 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["3", "1", "4", "9"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "30 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["6", "13", "16", "9"],
        answer: "6"
    },

{
        question: "72 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["8", "18", "22", "15"],
        answer: "18"
    },
    {
        question: "70 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["35", "14", "27", "43"],
        answer: "35"
    },
    {
        question: "96 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["3", "25", "20", "24"],
        answer: "24"
    },
    {
        question: "35 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["9", "11", "6", "5"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "45 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["10", "1", "3", "5"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "42 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["9", "6", "10", "5"],
        answer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "36 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["18", "17", "9", "2"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "27 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["3", "4", "11", "2"],
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "84 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["21", "22", "7", "24"],
        answer: "21"
    },
    {
        question: "56 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["12", "7", "4", "10"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "24 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["35", "12", "34", "24"],
        answer: "12"
    },
    {
        question: "76 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["25", "11", "2", "19"],
        answer: "19"
    },
    {
        question: "6 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["14", "1", "16", "13"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "42 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["12", "6", "10", "1"],
        answer: "6"
    },
    {
        question: "64 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["18", "10", "5", "16"],
        answer: "16"
    },
    {
        question: "69 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["16", "3", "22", "23"],
        answer: "23"
    },
    {
        question: "45 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["16", "9", "17", "15"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "81 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["9", "7", "5", "6"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "36 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["7", "11", "4", "6"],
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "24 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["7", "4", "3", "12"],
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "63 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["9", "14", "5", "4"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "58 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["11", "38", "21", "29"],
        answer: "29"
    },
    {
        question: "44 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["21", "5", "22", "11"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "63 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["3", "1", "4", "7"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "9 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["25", "3", "13", "6"],
        answer: "3"
    },

{
        question: "40 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["5", "11", "1", "3"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "88 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["7", "22", "24", "4"],
        answer: "22"
    },
    {
        question: "27 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["13", "3", "12", "9"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "42 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["14", "7", "16", "13"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "9 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["1", "9", "5", "3"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "70 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["10", "14", "3", "7"],
        answer: "10"
    },
    {
        question: "54 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["48", "27", "16", "45"],
        answer: "27"
    },
    {
        question: "28 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["18", "9", "7", "15"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "70 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["16", "5", "14", "17"],
        answer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "63 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["1", "11", "2", "7"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "45 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["11", "19", "2", "9"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "63 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["9", "3", "10", "13"],
        answer: "9"
    },
    {
        question: "82 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["33", "20", "41", "36"],
        answer: "41"
    },
    {
        question: "98 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["38", "11", "36", "49"],
        answer: "49"
    },
    {
        question: "55 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["11", "10", "15", "2"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "49 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["10", "2", "4", "7"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "10 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["5", "24", "46", "28"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "33 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["33", "3", "11", "4"],
        answer: "11"
    },
    {
        question: "28 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["22", "7", "2", "12"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "16 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["10", "11", "2", "3"],
        answer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "84 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["12", "14", "4", "6"],
        answer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "42 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["7", "9", "14", "1"],
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "40 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["1", "9", "3", "5"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "30 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["7", "9", "6", "5"],
        answer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "72 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["7", "2", "11", "9"],
        answer: "9"
    },

{
        question: "210 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["35", "131", "150", "41"],
        answer: "35"
    },
    {
        question: "880 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["55", "157", "176", "178"],
        answer: "176"
    },
    {
        question: "625 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["82", "125", "116", "119"],
        answer: "125"
    },
    {
        question: "651 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["206", "217", "54", "43"],
        answer: "217"
    },
    {
        question: "620 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["144", "30", "124", "192"],
        answer: "124"
    },
    {
        question: "632 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["170", "158", "54", "186"],
        answer: "158"
    },
    {
        question: "576 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["79", "64", "73", "41"],
        answer: "64"
    },
    {
        question: "594 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["37", "19", "66", "26"],
        answer: "66"
    },
    {
        question: "777 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["126", "111", "131", "128"],
        answer: "111"
    },
    {
        question: "216 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["74", "24", "30", "80"],
        answer: "24"
    },
    {
        question: "329 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["47", "111", "85", "34"],
        answer: "47"
    },
    {
        question: "900 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["103", "300", "234", "131"],
        answer: "300"
    },
    {
        question: "288 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["54", "74", "36", "109"],
        answer: "36"
    },
    {
        question: "579 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["193", "88", "116", "245"],
        answer: "193"
    },
    {
        question: "660 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["290", "226", "152", "220"],
        answer: "220"
    },
    {
        question: "920 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["73", "27", "107", "115"],
        answer: "115"
    },
    {
        question: "972 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["108", "82", "93", "68"],
        answer: "108"
    },
    {
        question: "500 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["58", "175", "163", "125"],
        answer: "125"
    },
    {
        question: "152 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["94", "19", "67", "101"],
        answer: "19"
    },
    {
        question: "792 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["88", "76", "15", "108"],
        answer: "88"
    },
    {
        question: "690 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["230", "262", "81", "134"],
        answer: "230"
    },
    {
        question: "248 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["25", "70", "31", "94"],
        answer: "31"
    },
    {
        question: "934 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["269", "482", "373", "467"],
        answer: "467"
    },
    {
        question: "441 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["96", "63", "20", "101"],
        answer: "63"
    },
    {
        question: "315 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["47", "59", "72", "35"],
        answer: "35"
    },

{
        question: "126 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["65", "79", "14", "58"],
        answer: "14"
    },
    {
        question: "640 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["32", "61", "80", "22"],
        answer: "80"
    },
    {
        question: "990 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["35", "11", "110", "87"],
        answer: "110"
    },
    {
        question: "990 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["53", "95", "50", "110"],
        answer: "110"
    },
    {
        question: "738 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["82", "77", "108", "28"],
        answer: "82"
    },
    {
        question: "500 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["53", "106", "250", "429"],
        answer: "250"
    },
    {
        question: "200 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["183", "303", "100", "207"],
        answer: "100"
    },
    {
        question: "580 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["116", "198", "199", "139"],
        answer: "116"
    },
    {
        question: "255 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["192", "75", "51", "108"],
        answer: "51"
    },
    {
        question: "332 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["123", "83", "220", "59"],
        answer: "83"
    },
    {
        question: "312 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["156", "267", "68", "295"],
        answer: "156"
    },
    {
        question: "570 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["167", "71", "114", "47"],
        answer: "114"
    },
    {
        question: "665 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["135", "154", "133", "156"],
        answer: "133"
    },
    {
        question: "981 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["327", "145", "238", "235"],
        answer: "327"
    },
    {
        question: "664 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["166", "137", "65", "120"],
        answer: "166"
    },
    {
        question: "180 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["75", "20", "46", "14"],
        answer: "20"
    },
    {
        question: "763 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["109", "58", "43", "91"],
        answer: "109"
    },
    {
        question: "672 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["48", "67", "96", "84"],
        answer: "84"
    },
    {
        question: "228 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["38", "146", "134", "139"],
        answer: "38"
    },
    {
        question: "117 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["304", "39", "119", "266"],
        answer: "39"
    },
    {
        question: "118 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["59", "395", "248", "446"],
        answer: "59"
    },
    {
        question: "623 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["89", "68", "102", "39"],
        answer: "89"
    },
    {
        question: "840 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["26", "84", "114", "105"],
        answer: "105"
    },
    {
        question: "586 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["258", "337", "293", "199"],
        answer: "293"
    },
    {
        question: "356 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["178", "341", "327", "273"],
        answer: "178"
    },

{
        question: "752 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["94", "96", "103", "34"],
        answer: "94",
    },
    {
        question: "342 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["38", "52", "35", "103"],
        answer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "774 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["258", "244", "184", "51"],
        answer: "258",
    },
    {
        question: "516 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["129", "86", "177", "159"],
        answer: "129",
    },
    {
        question: "752 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["376", "149", "444", "160"],
        answer: "376",
    },
    {
        question: "742 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["371", "340", "460", "51"],
        answer: "371",
    },
    {
        question: "424 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["53", "49", "54", "99"],
        answer: "53",
    },
    {
        question: "910 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["130", "77", "112", "132"],
        answer: "130",
    },
    {
        question: "176 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["44", "140", "115", "127"],
        answer: "44",
    },
    {
        question: "648 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["108", "55", "164", "88"],
        answer: "108",
    },
    {
        question: "567 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["189", "165", "319", "268"],
        answer: "189",
    },
    {
        question: "848 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["212", "99", "195", "112"],
        answer: "212",
    },
    {
        question: "732 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["122", "123", "19", "121"],
        answer: "122",
    },
    {
        question: "150 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["75", "303", "225", "444"],
        answer: "75",
    },
    {
        question: "342 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["57", "51", "132", "94"],
        answer: "57",
    },
    {
        question: "651 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["217", "201", "225", "224"],
        answer: "217",
    },
    {
        question: "805 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["115", "128", "36", "90"],
        answer: "115",
    },
    {
        question: "942 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["471", "443", "380", "349"],
        answer: "471",
    },
    {
        question: "147 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["21", "35", "86", "42"],
        answer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "340 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["68", "30", "147", "120"],
        answer: "68",
    },
    {
        question: "824 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["239", "412", "181", "439"],
        answer: "412",
    },
    {
        question: "528 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["66", "38", "100", "52"],
        answer: "66",
    },
    {
        question: "672 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["96", "70", "31", "23"],
        answer: "96",
    },
    {
        question: "568 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["71", "30", "25", "98"],
        answer: "71",
    },
    {
        question: "104 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["13", "109", "34", "17"],
        answer: "13",
    },

 {
        question: "632 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["83", "79", "82", "70"],
        answer: "79",
    },
    {
        question: "360 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["78", "90", "127", "154"],
        answer: "90",
    },
    {
        question: "672 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["219", "51", "168", "114"],
        answer: "168",
    },
    {
        question: "192 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["32", "160", "86", "113"],
        answer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "470 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["94", "22", "120", "95"],
        answer: "94",
    },
    {
        question: "775 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["40", "52", "155", "97"],
        answer: "155",
    },
    {
        question: "900 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["43", "105", "65", "150"],
        answer: "150",
    },
    {
        question: "867 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["305", "289", "72", "332"],
        answer: "289",
    },
    {
        question: "792 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["93", "44", "88", "86"],
        answer: "88",
    },
    {
        question: "696 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["60", "55", "87", "83"],
        answer: "87",
    },
    {
        question: "685 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["137", "179", "150", "86"],
        answer: "137",
    },
    {
        question: "884 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["83", "103", "67", "221"],
        answer: "221",
    },
    {
        question: "350 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["50", "135", "21", "82"],
        answer: "50",
    },
    {
        question: "506 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["94", "253", "470", "402"],
        answer: "253",
    },
    {
        question: "838 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["419", "107", "160", "373"],
        answer: "419",
    },
    {
        question: "852 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["70", "142", "111", "101"],
        answer: "142",
    },
    {
        question: "972 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["94", "108", "47", "24"],
        answer: "108",
    },
    {
        question: "852 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["213", "193", "192", "227"],
        answer: "213",
    },
    {
        question: "180 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["90", "178", "99", "138"],
        answer: "90",
    },
    {
        question: "276 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["41", "145", "69", "132"],
        answer: "69",
    },
    {
        question: "305 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["114", "63", "61", "138"],
        answer: "61",
    },
    {
        question: "345 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["117", "230", "115", "100"],
        answer: "115",
    },
    {
        question: "680 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["136", "197", "108", "84"],
        answer: "136",
    },
    {
        question: "792 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["45", "88", "17", "19"],
        answer: "88",
    },
    {
        question: "144 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["72", "309", "390", "135"],
        answer: "72",
    }, {
        question: "3532 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["883", "550", "745", "665"],
        answer: "883",
    },
    {
        question: "6627 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["1489", "2209", "893", "649"],
        answer: "2209",
    },
    {
        question: "6650 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["1243", "553", "1330", "1115"],
        answer: "1330",
    },
    {
        question: "5787 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["844", "1768", "1929", "995"],
        answer: "1929",
    },
    {
        question: "5558 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["966", "794", "895", "1387"],
        answer: "794",
    },
    {
        question: "2745 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["564", "305", "364", "344"],
        answer: "305",
    },
    {
        question: "1728 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["828", "1391", "1631", "288"],
        answer: "288",
    },
    {
        question: "2639 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["377", "1245", "1410", "1074"],
        answer: "377",
    },
    {
        question: "2073 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["1675", "2029", "691", "1385"],
        answer: "691",
    },
    {
        question: "2310 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["770", "2762", "1489", "705"],
        answer: "770",
    },
    {
        question: "7040 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["1223", "1156", "1186", "880"],
        answer: "880",
    },
    {
        question: "5112 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["1638", "1278", "394", "1165"],
        answer: "1278",
    },
    {
        question: "5792 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["598", "724", "645", "551"],
        answer: "724",
    },
    {
        question: "2448 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["1538", "1247", "636", "408"],
        answer: "408",
    },
    {
        question: "2436 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["444", "1400", "1604", "406"],
        answer: "406",
    },
    {
        question: "1398 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["2931", "466", "581", "3190"],
        answer: "466",
    },
    {
        question: "3878 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["1485", "2771", "4997", "1939"],
        answer: "1939",
    },
    {
        question: "2088 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["545", "649", "853", "261"],
        answer: "261",
    },
    {
        question: "2954 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["1477", "1691", "2958", "3533"],
        answer: "1477",
    },
    {
        question: "3231 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["233", "359", "285", "603"],
        answer: "359",
    },
    {
        question: "3826 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["4362", "618", "4876", "1913"],
        answer: "1913",
    },
    {
        question: "7050 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["663", "338", "1410", "1050"],
        answer: "1410",
    },
    {
        question: "2080 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["1743", "549", "1905", "520"],
        answer: "520",
    },
    {
        question: "5562 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["132", "618", "737", "545"],
        answer: "618",
    },
    {
        question: "3096 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["404", "1044", "344", "1104"],
        answer: "344",
    },

{
        question: "4460 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["4775", "2230", "4040", "4962"],
        answer: "2230",
    },
    {
        question: "7926 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["1551", "2642", "721", "1483"],
        answer: "2642",
    },
    {
        question: "6819 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["2273", "3164", "648", "867"],
        answer: "2273",
    },
    {
        question: "2595 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["865", "548", "1260", "2306"],
        answer: "865",
    },
    {
        question: "7245 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["1670", "656", "1449", "499"],
        answer: "1449",
    },
    {
        question: "3552 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["612", "952", "1230", "592"],
        answer: "592",
    },
    {
        question: "7191 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["497", "799", "270", "887"],
        answer: "799",
    },
    {
        question: "3660 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["3035", "1743", "1220", "1716"],
        answer: "1220",
    },
    {
        question: "1080 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["1288", "1171", "1121", "180"],
        answer: "180",
    },
    {
        question: "8486 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["4243", "4691", "4274", "4931"],
        answer: "4243",
    },
    {
        question: "4566 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["1412", "1619", "761", "935"],
        answer: "761",
    },
    {
        question: "6526 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["3589", "3263", "1229", "1448"],
        answer: "3263",
    },
    {
        question: "7504 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["1240", "1072", "885", "568"],
        answer: "1072",
    },
    {
        question: "6510 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["3188", "3255", "2773", "1179"],
        answer: "3255",
    },
    {
        question: "2176 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["2401", "544", "1961", "2483"],
        answer: "544",
    },
    {
        question: "7784 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["344", "973", "597", "262"],
        answer: "973",
    },
    {
        question: "9570 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["720", "1484", "1914", "836"],
        answer: "1914",
    },
    {
        question: "8424 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["795", "936", "985", "1104"],
        answer: "936",
    },
    {
        question: "6632 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["722", "352", "829", "1210"],
        answer: "829",
    },
    {
        question: "5648 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["1412", "2146", "617", "1488"],
        answer: "1412",
    },
    {
        question: "3800 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["1178", "1143", "858", "475"],
        answer: "475",
    },
    {
        question: "2114 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["1213", "1004", "201", "302"],
        answer: "302",
    },
    {
        question: "2552 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["1278", "638", "1356", "1149"],
        answer: "638",
    },
    {
        question: "8064 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["1403", "1152", "1208", "1352"],
        answer: "1152",
    },
    {
        question: "4784 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["624", "598", "530", "147"],
        answer: "598",
    },

{
        question: "9748 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["3947", "4874", "4499", "4613"],
        answer: "4874",
    },
    {
        question: "8008 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["1001", "1041", "910", "645"],
        answer: "1001",
    },
    {
        question: "9695 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["503", "415", "1385", "293"],
        answer: "1385",
    },
    {
        question: "5428 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["1800", "2714", "4606", "942"],
        answer: "2714",
    },
    {
        question: "7352 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["494", "1016", "919", "297"],
        answer: "919",
    },
    {
        question: "2823 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["1106", "2534", "1411", "941"],
        answer: "941",
    },
    {
        question: "2408 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["301", "1010", "785", "882"],
        answer: "301",
    },
    {
        question: "9328 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["1166", "597", "1053", "640"],
        answer: "1166",
    },
    {
        question: "7866 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["782", "459", "477", "1311"],
        answer: "1311",
    },
    {
        question: "8588 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["2099", "1139", "620", "2147"],
        answer: "2147",
    },
    {
        question: "9222 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["1223", "1467", "1425", "1537"],
        answer: "1537",
    },
    {
        question: "1395 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["155", "546", "637", "210"],
        answer: "155",
    },
    {
        question: "1492 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["1704", "1280", "2223", "373"],
        answer: "373",
    },
    {
        question: "4392 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["1098", "1259", "270", "1680"],
        answer: "1098",
    },
    {
        question: "2456 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["307", "1004", "560", "431"],
        answer: "307",
    },
    {
        question: "3876 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["1938", "4790", "1526", "3555"],
        answer: "1938",
    },
    {
        question: "7668 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["566", "852", "260", "899"],
        answer: "852",
    },
    {
        question: "8665 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["1733", "1625", "1920", "1406"],
        answer: "1733",
    },
    {
        question: "2460 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["615", "1742", "2151", "1722"],
        answer: "615",
    },
    {
        question: "2415 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["2505", "1467", "805", "2408"],
        answer: "805",
    },
    {
        question: "1330 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["190", "1365", "1209", "1237"],
        answer: "190",
    },
    {
        question: "8164 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["2356", "380", "1064", "2041"],
        answer: "2041",
    },
    {
        question: "2675 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["478", "562", "535", "1722"],
        answer: "535",
    },
    {
        question: "2472 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["1533", "860", "412", "971"],
        answer: "412",
    },
    {
        question: "2688 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["689", "981", "672", "1578"],
        answer: "672",
    },

{
        question: "1210 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["1803", "995", "1534", "242"],
        answer: "242",
    },
    {
        question: "4666 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["2730", "2333", "2586", "2005"],
        answer: "2333",
    },
    {
        question: "7328 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["4159", "4278", "3664", "3046"],
        answer: "3664",
    },
    {
        question: "8985 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["2563", "2995", "1800", "1031"],
        answer: "2995",
    },
    {
        question: "8300 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["1497", "1660", "1619", "1189"],
        answer: "1660",
    },
    {
        question: "2317 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["228", "1076", "157", "331"],
        answer: "331",
    },
    {
        question: "1200 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["255", "150", "374", "237"],
        answer: "150",
    },
    {
        question: "4600 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["2300", "2099", "1725", "1909"],
        answer: "2300",
    },
    {
        question: "9597 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["1371", "849", "273", "338"],
        answer: "1371",
    },
    {
        question: "9982 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["4991", "1929", "629", "2072"],
        answer: "4991",
    },
    {
        question: "4784 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["523", "598", "182", "994"],
        answer: "598",
    },
    {
        question: "8776 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["2882", "3788", "4388", "3780"],
        answer: "4388",
    },
    {
        question: "8464 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["2216", "340", "678", "2116"],
        answer: "2116",
    },
    {
        question: "5108 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["855", "1829", "1277", "2314"],
        answer: "1277",
    },
    {
        question: "4809 / 3 = ?",
        options: ["1603", "3039", "2985", "3152"],
        answer: "1603",
    },
    {
        question: "2070 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["639", "1923", "4333", "1035"],
        answer: "1035",
    },
    {
        question: "4176 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["435", "1568", "696", "1047"],
        answer: "696",
    },
    {
        question: "9770 / 5 = ?",
        options: ["1265", "1191", "1954", "983"],
        answer: "1954",
    },
    {
        question: "2079 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["381", "597", "255", "231"],
        answer: "231",
    },
    {
        question: "2821 / 7 = ?",
        options: ["403", "1342", "1066", "159"],
        answer: "403",
    },
    {
        question: "4560 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["760", "1177", "913", "1306"],
        answer: "760",
    },
    {
        question: "3882 / 6 = ?",
        options: ["647", "1574", "323", "806"],
        answer: "647",
    },
    {
        question: "6482 / 2 = ?",
        options: ["1734", "4888", "3241", "4516"],
        answer: "3241",
    },
    {
        question: "6744 / 8 = ?",
        options: ["707", "371", "931", "843"],
        answer: "843",
    },
    {
        question: "9496 / 4 = ?",
        options: ["2374", "2406", "2024", "319"],
        answer: "2374",
    },
];

export default level18questions;
